{
    "id": "2b49fc9cba3f47959b9baf8984c5ff8a",
    "title": "The Positive, Comparative And Superlative Degree",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How is your mother today? Is she any …………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "44d2cac4428b4a87a0f69ae13ccc8591"
        },
        {
            "question": "In India May is …………………………… than June.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "hotter",
                "hottest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "de61a5c5704a4bb08576ef9e8ef21256"
        },
        {
            "question": "Julie is ………………………….. than her sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettier",
                "prettiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b1428434cef400c89ead2945b91c64a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the ………………………… girl in your class?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beautiful",
                "most beautiful",
                "more beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48d8d1f9f349494eadd2a6de13df1c2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the ………………………….. of all metals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "precious",
                "more precious",
                "most precious"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aa4c6a5768db4abe8bfec591b2874e67"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her husband is ten years ……………………………… than her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "older",
                "oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc73f652494b4832b25c7e5f51ba912a"
        },
        {
            "question": "All of us are bad singers, but I sing the ………………………….. of all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "worse",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d0031b85917c45429040fd4604daa6d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think you require a ………………………….. diet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nutritious",
                "more nutritious",
                "most nutritious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "611f3d081a1b4873a11ed8106ecd1ab9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the ………………………… part of India?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dry",
                "drier",
                "driest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "84af133d72194bbc90be0f7cd51981ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the ……………………….. moment of my life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "proud",
                "prouder",
                "proudest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f13ca3492c04c2ab0971f196ab49b69"
        }
    ]
}